fungamesonlinegames.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy

| 

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive. 

**General**

Registration is not required to enter our site.

**Use of Information**

Like most servers, our servers automatically record the page requests made when a user visits this site. These "server logs" typically include your web request (the requested content), IP address, browser type, browser language and the date and time of your request.  
We may use these IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly. 

Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better service to you. We may use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on this website. We will use session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognize you when you visit. 

We use companies to serve the advertisements on some of our pages. These companies and advertisers may place and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. We may use your information or allow advertisers or companies that serve advertisements access to your information to determine which advertisements you will see. This information may include your demographic information, geographic location, what content you access on our site, how you rate various content and other information. 

Our site contains links, including banner and other ads, to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites if they are not under our control. 

We use this information to help diagnose problems, to analyze statistics of our site, and to allow us to improve the overall user-experience. 

We do not sell or disclose email addresses or any other personal information about you. 

**Information Sharing**

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us. 

However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety. 

In the event that we acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. 

**Google Analytics**

This site makes use of Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. This site may also make use of other Google Analytics for Display Advertising features, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting and/or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. We are required by Google to disclose the following information to you in our Privacy Statement in connection with our use of any Google Analytics for Display Advertising features on this website: 

You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising or customize Google Display Network ads by using the 

. You may also prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics by opting out through the use of the 

.

If we make use of the Google Analytics for Display Advertising Remarketing feature, we will use such Remarketing feature to advertise online and third party vendors, including Google, may show ads for this site on sites across the web.

This site and third party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on a user's past visits to this site, and/or (b) report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to this website. 

Data from Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting may be utilized by us to help recognize and understand user preferences, to make improvements to this site, to choose content and advertising to display to you, and for other business purposes that will allow us to better serve you.

**DoubleClick DART and Third-Party Vendors Cookies**

This site also may use DART and third-party vendors cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART cookies use "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting 

Third parties, like Google, may collect certain types of information about visits to the site, including interaction with content on these sites. As always, no personally identifiable information will be collected. 

**Flash shared objects:**

Most games on this site are based on flash technology (flash games). Flash games may collect data in "shared objects" which are text-files stored on your computer. We have no control over what data flash games of third parties may collect. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties flash games. You can delete stored data on your computer by this website or all websites information on your computer with Macromedias "Settings Manager" for Adobe Flash Player by visiting: 

**Other**

We may present internal links (i.e. links to our own pages) or external links (i.e. links to other websites) in a format that allows us to track statistics like the number of clicks a link gets. These statistics will only be used to help us improve the site. 

We protect personal information against such risks as loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, modification or destruction, through appropriate security measures. 

**Use of Social Plugins**

The responsible entity uses social plugins ("plugins") of the social networks Facebook and Google on its website from facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, United States ("Facebook"), twitter.com, which is operated by Twitter Inc. 795 Folsom Street, Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, United States ("Twitter") and google.com, which is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, California, 94043, United States ("Google+1"). The plugins are marked with their logos: Facebook, Twitter and Google+1. If a user visits a page on this website, which contains such a plugin, the browser builds up a direct link to the Facebook, Twitter or Google servers. The contents of the plugin is from Facebook, Twitter and Google directly to the browser of the customer and integrated into this website. By integrating these plugins Facebook, Twitter and Google receive information that the customer has visited this website. If the customer is logged into Facebook, Twitter or Google, these companies can assign the visit of the website to his or her Facebook/Twitter/Google account. When the customer interacts with the plugins, for example, the "Like" button, "Tweet" button, "+1 Button" or add a comment, the corresponding information from the client's browser is sent directly to Facebook, Twitter or Google and stored there. Purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of data through Facebook, Twitter or Google are related to the settings of the customer to protect his privacy, refer to the privacy policies of Facebook, Twitter or Google. 

**Binding Agreement**

Your use of our site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy. By using this site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page.  
  
---|---
